step2.com 2016-07-22

# Privacy at Step2

Effective Date: 3/11/2016 

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, www.step2.com and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the website. 

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

You'd be hard pressed to find a company that values your privacy more than The Step2 Company, LLC (collectively, "We", "Us", "Our" or "Step2") does. When you visit our website you will be given the opportunity to receive email from us. We know that some of the information you choose to give us is personal, and we take that seriously. Read the statement below if you'd like to know what we do with the information we obtain from you. 

This privacy statement describes how The Step2 Company, LLC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.step2.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

**Personal Information About You**

When you send us personal information such as your email address, street address, etc., we use this information for limited and specific purposes including the following: 

1\. We combine your information with data submitted by others. We use this aggregated data to analyze purchase trends and identify common characteristics of our customers such as what states they live in, etc. Your data is not personally identifiable at this point - you are anonymous. 

2\. We use this combined, anonymous information, along with any comments you provide, to help develop new products and make adjustments to current products. Again, this information is analyzed collectively and is not personally identifiable. 

3\. We also may use anonymous information to help persuade retailers to carry our products. We do not lend, rent or sell personally-identifiable information to our retailers. 

4\. In order to place an order you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). 

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide additional contact information (such phone number and shipping address) and financial information (such as shipping address if different than your and credit card number). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

5\. If you request that we follow up with you personally such as to help you find a Step2 retailer or to fix a problem with a product, then we, or someone working specifically for us, will use this information to contact you as you requested. 

6\. If you choose to receive email or promotional information via postal mail from Step2, then occasionally (usually no more than twice a month), we will send you email or mail about Step2 products and promotions. We won't clog your mailbox with a bunch of spam, and we won't give your email address or postal address to anyone else. That's just not our style. 

**How to be Removed from Our Mailing List**

If you wish to be removed from our list, please [click here to contact us](mailto:step2-company@step2.net). If you prefer, you may call us toll-free at 866-429-5200 or by write to us at the address below: 

**The Step2 Company**  
**10010 Aurora-Hudson Road**  
**Streetsboro, Ohio 44241**  
**U.S.A.**

You may also follow the unsubscribe instructions located within all of the email communications you receive. If you have registered for an account you may also log into your account and manage your email subscriptions by choosing the "profile and subscriptions" section and identifying which specific type of communications you'd like to receive. 

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

**Access to Personal Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by making the change on our member information page (if you have registered for an account on www.step2.com) or by emailing our Customer Support at [Step2-Company@Step2.net](mailto:Step2-Company@Step2.net) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed above. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Special Notice for Parents: Personal Information About Your Children**

We are extremely concerned about your children's privacy. We do not knowingly collect any personal information directly from children, and we do not knowingly place children on our mailing list. 

When you register we may ask for some general information about your children or grandchildren. Specifically, we may ask for age and gender information. We combine this information with data submitted by other customers. This aggregated data is not personally identifiable. It is anonymous. 

We use this combined, anonymous information to help us better understand who is using our products. Knowing this helps us develop new products and make adjustments to current products. Again, this information is analyzed collectively and is not personally identifiable. 

We never ask for your children's names or anything that could be used to contact them personally. Under no circumstances is any information you provide used to knowingly market directly to your children or to contact your children. If you have reason to believe that a child's Personal Information was provided to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information and terminate the child's account from our databases. 

**Tracking Technologies**

We The Step2 Company, LLC and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or technology service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g. language preference), and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited. 

**Log Files**

When you visit our website we detect and may record how you got here and where you came from. Specifically, we may collect the domain name or IP address of the site from which you connected, the type of browser you used, and what search terms you used if you found our site(s) via a search engine or link. This information is not used to identify you personally. This information is combined and analyzed anonymously to determine how and when people are visiting our website. We also use this information to measure the performance of our site and to help us decide where to advertise our brand and products. 

**Flash & HTML5**

We use Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use Flash cookies and HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

**Behavioral Advertising**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We will not give your email address to anyone else.

We DO NOT disclose any personally identifiable information about you to anyone not doing work specifically for Step2 such as a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, and a customer service provider to manage our help section. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. An exception to this is when we believe in good faith that we are required to disclose such information by a law enforcement agency or court of law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial or bankruptcy proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

In the event Step2 goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Also, as we explained above, we may combine information you provide with data from others. We may use this combined information to help persuade retailers to carry our products. The information we share with our retailers is collective and completely anonymous. 

On a very limited basis, we may allow carefully selected marketing partners to send postal mailings to members who have signed up to be on our direct mail list. These companies will never be given your email address and will not have access to any information about you other than your postal mailing address. If you wish to opt out of receiving these postal mailings you may do so by emailing us at [Step2-Company@Step2.net](mailto:Step2-Company@Step2.net). 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our www.step2.com order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [Step2-Company@Step2.net](mailto:Step2-Company@Step2.net). 

**Links to Other Websites**

Our Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Step2. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit. 

**Reviews**

All review content on www.step2.com is provided by PowerReviews. All submission and use of reviews and ratings is subject to PowerReviews' policies, including its Terms of Use, Usage Agreement, and Privacy Policy, available at <http://www.powerreviews.com/legal/>. Reviews posted at www.Step2.com may also be displayed at [Buzzillions.com](http://www.buzzillions.com/4294903459_4294965645_nz_toys_games_hobbies_reviews). 

If you wish to have your product review removed you may contact us at [Step2-Company@Step2.net](mailto:Step2-Company@Step2.net).

**Public Forums**

Our website may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [Step2-Company@Step2.net](mailto:Step2-Company@Step2.net). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Social Media Features and Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Single Sign-on**

You can log in to our website using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us, and to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

**Collection and Use of Third Party Personal Information**

You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name, shipping address and phone number. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided. To request removal of such third party personal information from our database, contact us at [Step2-Company@Step2.net](mailto:Step2-Company@Step2.net). 

**Contest**

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personal information for any other purpose. We will not share the personal information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

**Your Acceptance**

When you use our website, you acknowledge your acceptance of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use our website. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [Step2-Company@Step2.net](mailto:Step2-Company@Step2.net) or 10010 Aurora-Hudson Road, Streetsboro, OH 44241
